farrahgray.com 2019-05-17

# Privacy Policy – Farrah Gray

At Farrah Gray (“Farrah Gray” or “We” or “we”), we are sensitive to the privacy concerns of visitors to our website. Farrah Gray is committed to keeping your personal information private. Because our website includes areas in which individuals can provide personally identifiable information, we have developed the Farrah Gray Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) to inform you of our policies and practices regarding information we collect about you on our website.

This Privacy Policy applies to Farrah Gray and all its affiliate companies. This Privacy Policy explains how we handle your personal information collected via our website or entered by you in connection with your use of our website. Through of use of our website you are accepting our Privacy Policy and expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective on posting, as amended from time to time.

**Information Collected**  
We may collect and store the following categories of personal information:

  * E-mail address, mailing address, and other physical contact information 
  * Transactional information based on your activities on our website; 
  * Correspondence transmitted by you to Farrah Gray via our website; and 
  * Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from our website, IP addresses (see below) and standard web log information.

**Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses**  
Our website collects or logs certain information that cannot identify you personally when you site our website. This information includes your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address and your domain name. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by the ISP company through which you access the Web. A domain name is the name of the ISP company through which you access the Web.

Our website logs IP addresses and domain names and aggregates them for system administration and monitoring the use of our website. We use the aggregated information to measure the number of visits to our website, the average time spent on our website, the number of pages viewed, and various other website use statistics. This monitoring helps us evaluate how our website is used and allows us to continuously improve the content we provide. Our website does not link IP addresses or domain names with any personally identifiable information which means that a visitor’s session will be logged on our servers but the visitor will always remain anonymous.

**Cookies**  
We may use cookies or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience on our website. Cookies are pieces of information that a web server may transfer to your computer through your web browser. When this information is stored on your computer, our system is able to recognize your browser and, in turn, customize web content for you. You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your web browser. However, if you chose to reject cookies, you may not be able to use certain online services or features of our website.

**How Information is Collected**  
Farrah Gray may collect personal information from you when you visit or use our website in the following ways:

  * When you visit our website, certain technical information (IP address and domain name) is collected by the website. This technical information does not identify you personally. 
  * When you visit our website, you may request information about Farrah Gray or its products. When you make such a request for further information you will be asked to provide Farrah Gray with certain personal information, such as your e-mail address, mailing address and/or other personal information. 

**How Information is Used**  
Farrah Gray uses your personal information obtained via our website in the following ways:

  * To provide you with information about Farrah Gray. If you do not wish to be contacted directly by Farrah Gray to receive further information, please contact us at: [privacy@farrahgray.com](https://wcc.secureserver.net/email?).  To contact you in response to any requests, questions, complaints, or comments you may have made about Farrah Gray or our website.
  * For internal purposes of Farrah Gray, including marketing assessment, list management, and demographic matching with other internal database information. 
  * To evaluate your credentials or skills for the purpose of an employment position for which you may have applied.

Except as specifically stated in this Privacy Policy, Farrah Gray does not use personal information for purposes other than the purpose for which the personal information is collected. Farrah Gray has developed and implemented policies and procedures that restrict the access and use of personal information based on the specific roles and duties of each member of the Farrah Gray organization.

**What Information is Shared**  
Except as described below, our website does not collect or compile personal information for distribution to parties outside of Farrah Gray.

  * We will disclose personal information to comply with valid legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order, or to protect our rights and property. We will disclose information when we believe in good faith that the law requires such disclosure. 
  * Farrah Gray also will disclose your personal information when necessary to comply with applicable laws, rules or regulations, when you have expressly consented to such disclosure, or when necessary to preserve Farrah Gray’s legal rights in the Site’s content.
  * We don’t sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies (such as demographic data) to improve and personalize our services.
  * You will not receive any contact from third parties outside of Farrah Gray as a result of providing information to us. 

**Updating or Deleting Personal Information**  
You may request Farrah Gray to update your personal information collected via the Site or delete personal information previously transmitted by you to Farrah Gray via the Site. You should be aware that it may not be technologically possible to remove or verify each and every record of information you have provided to us from our system. The need to back-up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your personal information may exist in archived systems. However, promptly after receiving your request, all personal information stored in databases we actively use and other readily searchable media will be updated, corrected, changed, deleted or confirmed to you, as appropriate, as soon as reasonably practicable. Farrah Gray will take all commercially reasonable steps to remove any personal information stored on our systems if you so request. If you would like to update information previously submitted to Farrah Gray or request to have personal information deleted, please e-mail us at [privacy@farrahgray.com](https://wcc.secureserver.net/email?) or mail us at:

**Contact Us**

**Farrah Gray**

**PO Box 33355**

**Las Vegas, NV 89133**

**Attention: Ms. Logan**

**+1-702-878-8665**

**Consent to the Terms of this Privacy Policy**  
By using this site and providing us with information you agree to all the terms of the Farrah Gray Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any term of the Farrah Gray Privacy Policy, please do not use our site or submit any personally identifiable information.

**Modifications or Revisions of this Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to change or replace the Farrah Gray Privacy Policy at our sole discretion. Please check our site from time to time to ensure that you are aware of any changes or updates to the Farrah Gray Privacy Policy. Should you have any questions about the Farrah Gray Privacy Policy or our collection or use of information through this site, please contact us at [privacy@farrahgray.com](https://wcc.secureserver.net/email?).

**Protection of Children**  
Farrah Gray understands the importance of protecting children’s privacy, especially in an online environment. Our website is not intentionally designed for or directed at children 13 years of age or younger. It is Farrah Gray’s policy to never knowingly collect or maintain information about individuals 13 years of age or younger.

**Links and Third Party Sites**  
Our website may contain links to other Internet website. Farrah Gray does not endorse and is not responsible for, the privacy practices or the content of third party website. You should review the applicable privacy policies in connection with your use of such third party website. To the extent that our website contains links to third party payment or transaction processing services, you understand that Farrah Gray is not responsible for the protection of information transmitted to the third party payment or transaction processing service, nor is Farrah Gray responsible for approving/disapproving, facilitating or consummating any transaction or payment you make through the use of such third party payment or transaction processing service.

**Security**  
We treat data as an asset that must be protected and we use tools to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure, including use of physical access controls, Internet firewalls, intrusion detection, and network monitoring. However, as you know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from our website. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**Notice to California Residents**

If you are a resident of the State of California, California Civil Code Section 1798.8, known as the “ _Shine the Light”_ Act permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by Farrah Gray to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. With respect to these entities, this Privacy Policy applies only to their activities within the State of California. All inquiries regarding the California “Shine the Light” law should be sent to [privacy@farrahgray.com](https://wcc.secureserver.net/email?) with “California Privacy Information Request” on the subject line and in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you at your e-mail address in response.
